<root>
  <content id="types">
    <p>There are four types of page types. static, suite, test and project pages.</p>
    <img src="images/doc/run01.png"/>
    <ul>
      <li>static pages were skipped in test runs.</li>
      <li>suite pages runs amount of test pages which runs automatically. test pages contains all information about a
        test and the test itself.
      </li>
      <li>project pages contains only some project informations, but they differently in the configuration. In project
        and suite pages you can configure node specific base url for every selenium node.
      </li>
    </ul>
    <p>This is interesting for paralell test runs.</p>
    <h3>
      <a id="screenshot-settings" class="anchor" href="#screenshot-settings" aria-hidden="true">
        <span aria-hidden="true" class="octicon octicon-link"></span>
      </a>
      Screenshot settings
    </h3>
    <img src="images/doc/config02.png"></img>
    <p>Besides being able to use the command
      <em>captureEntirePageScreenshot</em>
      at any time, you have opportunity taking screenshot automatically. This can be defined after each test or after
      every single command.
    </p>
    <h3>
      <a id="header-and-footer" class="anchor" href="#header-and-footer" aria-hidden="true">
        <span aria-hidden="true" class="octicon octicon-link"></span>
      </a>
      Headerand Footer
    </h3>
    <p>There are three types of header and footers.</p>
    <p>page header and footer, test header and footer and the last one, suite header and footer. pages with titles<em>
      pageHeader</em>and<em>pageFooter</em>are include automaticaly in actual page context.<em>setUp</em>and<em>
      tearDown</em>pages are only includes in pages from type
      <em>test</em>
      <em>suiteSetUp</em>and<em>suitTearDown</em>are only includes in pages from type<em>Suite</em>If the included pages
      have selenium testcases, so they will run as a normal test.At this point you must look out at the "close command"
      in included files, otherwise all upcomming tests wherefailing.
    </p>
  </content>
</root>